<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MedellinSites</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="main">Main Menu</string>

    <string-array name="menu">
        <item>Cinema</item>
        <item>Theaters</item>
        <item>Restaurants</item>
        <item>Partys</item>
        <item>Touristic Sites</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="menu_s">
        <item>This is cinemas</item>
        <item>This is theaters</item>
        <item>This is restaurants</item>
        <item>This is partys</item>
        <item>This is touristic Sites</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="menucine">
        <item>Procinal</item>
        <item>RoyalFIlms</item>
        <item>CineColombia</item>
    </string-array>


    <string name="item">Menu</string>
    <string name="item2">Menu2</string>

    <string name="but1">Facebook</string>
    <string name="but2">Webpage</string>
    <string name="but3">Programation</string>

    <string name="cine1info">From our seats the movie looks better</string>
    <string name="cine2info">Royal Films is a family company that started only with a theater in the heart of the city of Barranquilla,
        but it was not enough to place a new entertainment; also become as a culture the hobby of Colombians; because of this, through
        the years we have grown up expanding our horizons by building new cinemas and shopping centers, which has allowed us to project
        into the future and have a presence in the top five Colombian film companies.</string>
    <string name="cine3info">The most important distribution company in Colombia, with 46% participation in the national market distribution,
        distribute to Colombia FOX and Warner as well as independent films that takes in the most important markets worldwide.</string>
    <string name="sed1">Sede 1</string>
    <string name="sed2">Sede 2</string>
    <string name="sed3">Sede 3</string>
    <string name="sed4">Sede 4</string>
    <string name="back">Return</string>

    <string name="titt1">Teatro Metropolitano</string>
    <string name="titt2">Pequeño Teatro</string>
    <string name="teat1info">You are welcome to the Metropolitan Theater where you willl find the best cultural events in Medellin</string>
    <string name="teat2info">Pequeño Teatro is projected as a culturl space, a reference city open to all artistic practices and
        a meeting point of the movement and the tradition of the performing arts of Medellin.</string>
    <string name="teat3info">The Teatro Pablo Tobon Uribe is a theater of Medellin, Colombia, located on La Playa avenue.
        It has been one of the most traditional scenario of the city, offers a varied programation throughout the year, it was
        inaugurated on August 2, 1967, and has the best acoustics to offer for musical and theatrical performances.</string>

    <string name="restaur1">El Rancherito</string>
    <string name="restaur2">Mondongos</string>
    <string name="restaur3">Frutos del Mar</string>
    <string name="rest1info">The flavor of our menu retains the traditional recipes of her grandmother, flavors that are the result of the
        mixture of ingredients that always have the best quality... are products selected very carefully every day.\t\n
        In our kitchens the preparations are made every day and by employees who live in the areas surrounding each point ...
        so we also get an ingredient in each preparation which is the affection, the taste and love with which everyone work. ..</string>
    <string name="rest2info">\tTo speak of Mondongos is to talk of a whole culture and to refer, as an emblem and an institution,
        to a Restaurant that receives hundreds of local and foreign patrons every day.\n\t
        All this speciality that Mondongos puts together and that is a faithful tertimony of the valuer that transcend in our culture in
        Antioquia, give more than one reason to the artists of our country an those who visit us, to have us as one of their sure destinations,
        and, without exception, come to visit us on their stays in Medellín</string>
    <string name="rest3info">THE TRUE TASTE OF THE SEA IN YOUR PALATE\t\n
        FRUTOS DEL MAR is a line of restaurants specializing in seafood and Distribution of Fish and shellfish.</string>

    <string name="rumba1">Tibiri Tabara</string>
    <string name="rumba2">La Ruana de Juana</string>
    <string name="rumba3">La Garganta</string>
    <string name="rum1info">The Tibiri Bar is the best Afro Caribbean music of the city, there anyonecan be your dance partner between
        discharges, son or guaguancos.
        It is small, it is a basement and is hot like in a Caribbean island, but if you let yourself envolve by the atmosphere, the property
        fraternity of our neighboorhoods, you will be agree with us, that there the happines make it self movement, music and sweat.</string>
    <string name="rum2info">La Ruana de Juana excels for having a happy and fun decoration with an atmosphere of fonda unique in the city, where
         you will find the best parties and the most beautiful women of Colombia.
        Is the best club in the Lleras. We offer national and imported liquors at the best price in the sector.\n\n\t
        Our motto "Pongaselo de Ruana" invites all it is costumers to enjoy the best nigth with excellent service.</string>
    <string name="rum3info">La Garganta always innovating with the best crossover parties in La 33, no cover.</string>

    <string name="turi1">Museo de Antioquia</string>
    <string name="turi2">Jardín Botánico</string>
    <string name="turi3">Cerro Nuti</string>
    <string name="turi1info">Museo de Antioquia, where you will find all activities, programs and events that are developed inside
        the institution, a description of permanent, temporary (current, future and past) exhibitions. Special guests, academics and
        cultural meetings, interviews, profiles, among other productions.</string>
    <string name="turi2info">The Medellin Botanical Garden Joaquín Antonio Uribe constitutes it self as one of the most beautiful and
        important living museums of our country. It is considered a show for its visitors at any time of year. The Botanical Garden
        is a place to relax and contemplate its enormous floral wealth, since it has the largest collection of orchids of the entire city,
        also it houses more than 1,000 animals and plant species. It also has an auditorium, library, museums and a wide zone for food to
        visitors.</string>
    <string name="turi3info">It is one of the most important and famous hills of the city. It is billed as the largest natural park in
        the urban area. On it there are three big turistic attractions of Medellin: The Pueblito Paisa, the outdoor theater "Carlos Vieco"
        and Sculpture Park. It is meeting place for family outings, friends and tourists, particularly at weekends and in December. Its
        footpaths are crowded, even by athletes amounting there every day.</string>

<!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_cinemas">cinemas</string>
    <string name="title_activity_theaters">theaters</string>
    <string name="title_activity_restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="title_activity_rparty">rparty</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tours">tours</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
</resources>
